UNITE Jeff Eichler Files 6000/030
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE Jeff Eichler Files
1994-1999
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE)
Eichler, Jeff
6000/030
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records.
8239569
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 17, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 17, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6000 AV 6000 G: UNITE Posters 6000 MB: UNITE Memorabilia 6000 P: UNITE Photographs 6000 PUBS: UNITE Publications
Eichler, Jeff; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees
8239569
- Harrisburg PA, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Passaic, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Mercer County - NJ, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Hudson County, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Gloucester County, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Deptford Township - Bill Bain, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Bergin County, 1994-1998 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Notes on Meeting with St. Louis Procurement official, Corresp., Info on St. Louis Procurement, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Uniform Meeting, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Minneapolis, Mn, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Baltimore/MD (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Banyor, ME, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Bangor, ME Sweatshop Legislation - 1997 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Fall River/ MA, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Bidderford, ME, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Local 6, ILWU, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Firefighters, Local 798, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Muni - TWU, Local 200, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Parking - Traffic, Local 790, SEIU, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Police - SF, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Postal Unions NACL/APWU, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- CV Smith Product, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- San Jose, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- San Jose/Police, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- PG&E San Jose, California Brill, Bill (Box 1, Folder 25)
- UNIT06 - CA (Box 1, Folder 26)
- UNITE Company Specs., 1998 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- California, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Los Angeles, CA, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- SF: Local Production Resolution, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- San Francisco CA, Code of Conduct for Purchasing - 1997 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- UNITE!, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- "Directory of Products made by Former ACTWU Members", 1997 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Labor Books, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 34)